{
    "chapter_metadata": {
        "chapter_id": "5.English.28",
        "standard": "5",
        "subject": "English Balbharati",
        "medium": "English",
        "chapter_name": "All about Money"
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_id": 1,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What do we need to buy things?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Paper",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Money",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Water",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Air",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Money"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 2,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is the currency of the United States?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Rupees",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Pounds",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Dollars",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Yen",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Dollars"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 3,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is the currency of England?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Rupees",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Pounds",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Dollars",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Euro",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Pounds"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 4,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is the currency of India?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Rupees",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Dollars",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Pounds",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Dinar",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Rupees"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 5,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is the system of exchanging one thing for another known as?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Banking",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Barter",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Selling",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Buying",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Barter"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 6,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Which of these was used as money in the past?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Plastic cards",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Smartphones",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Shells and cowries",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Computers",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Shells and cowries"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 7,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What precious metals were used as money?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Iron and Steel",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Gold, silver, and copper",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Aluminium",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Plastic",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Gold, silver, and copper"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 8,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Where was paper money first used?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "India",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "China",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "USA",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "England",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "China"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 9,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "About how many years ago was paper money used in China?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "100 years",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "500 years",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "1000 years",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "10 years",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "1000 years"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 10,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is 'Cash Money'?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Credit cards",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Coins and notes",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Checks",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Gold bars",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Coins and notes"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 11,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Do paper notes have value of their own material?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Yes, very high",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "No, they have no value of their own",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Sometimes",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "It depends",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "No, they have no value of their own"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 12,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is a note really?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "A photograph",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "A 'promise' to give that much money",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "A toy",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "A bill",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "A 'promise' to give that much money"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 13,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Who prints the notes?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Anyone",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Banks only",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "The government",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Schools",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "The government"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 14,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What should you NOT do with notes?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Spend them",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Save them",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Write on, tear or crumple them",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Count them",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Write on, tear or crumple them"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 15,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Which of these are living things?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Tables",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Plants and animals",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Stones",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Water",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Plants and animals"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 16,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What are animals that lay eggs called?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Viviparous",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Oviparous",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Mammals",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Herbivores",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Oviparous"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 17,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What are animals that give birth to young ones called?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Viviparous",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Oviparous",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Birds",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Reptiles",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Viviparous"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 18,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What type of diagram is used to show classification?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Circle diagram",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Tree diagram",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Map",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Painting",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Tree diagram"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 19,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Which coins are listed in the diagram?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "50 p, 1, 5, 10 rupee",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "100 rupee coin",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "1 cent",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "1000 rupee coin",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "50 p, 1, 5, 10 rupee"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 20,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Which note had the highest value in the diagram?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Five hundred",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Two thousand",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "One thousand",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Fifty",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Two thousand"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 21,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What did people use before metals?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Only notes",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Grain, cattle, stones, salt",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Plastic",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Cars",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Grain, cattle, stones, salt"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 22,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "Why did people switch to metal money?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "It was heavier",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "It was easier to carry",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "It was edible",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "It was colorful",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "It was easier to carry"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 23,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is an 'autobiography'?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "A story written by oneself about one's life",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "A story about cars",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "A fairy tale",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "A science book",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "A story written by oneself about one's life"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 24,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What symbol is used for Indian Rupee?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "$",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "£",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "₹",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "¥",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "₹"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 25,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What symbol is used for Dollar?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "$",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "£",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "₹",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "€",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "$"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 26,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What symbol is used for Pound?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "$",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "£",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "₹",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "¥",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "£"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 27,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "How do you earn money?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "It grows on trees",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "You have to work hard for it",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "It falls from sky",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "You find it everywhere",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "You have to work hard for it"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 28,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What is 'crumple'?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "To fold neatly",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "To crush into wrinkles",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "To tear",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "To wash",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "To crush into wrinkles"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 29,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What are 'implements'?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Tools",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Toys",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Clothes",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Food",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Tools"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 30,
            "question_type": "MCQ",
            "question": "What are the two types of plants mentioned?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_id": 1,
                    "text": "Big and Small",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 2,
                    "text": "Flowering and Non-flowering",
                    "is_correct": true
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 3,
                    "text": "Green and Red",
                    "is_correct": false
                },
                {
                    "option_id": 4,
                    "text": "Land and Water",
                    "is_correct": false
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Flowering and Non-flowering"
        },
        {
            "question_id": 31,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What do we use money for?",
            "answer": "To buy things and pay people."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 32,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Which country uses the Dollar?",
            "answer": "The United States."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 33,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Which country uses the Pound?",
            "answer": "England."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 34,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Which country uses the Rupee?",
            "answer": "India."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 35,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is barter?",
            "answer": "Exchanging one thing for another."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 36,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Name one item used as money in the past (besides metals).",
            "answer": "Salt / Shells / Stones."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 37,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Name a precious metal used for money.",
            "answer": "Gold / Silver / Copper."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 38,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Who invented paper money?",
            "answer": "China."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 39,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Who prints currency notes?",
            "answer": "The government."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 40,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "How should you treat money/notes?",
            "answer": "Carefully."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 41,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'currency'?",
            "answer": "Cash money (coins and notes)."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 42,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What note comes after 100 in the list?",
            "answer": "Two hundred."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 43,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What note comes after 500 in the list?",
            "answer": "Two thousand."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 44,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What coin is smaller than 1 rupee?",
            "answer": "Fifty-paise coin."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 45,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are living things divided into?",
            "answer": "Plants and animals."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 46,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are the two types of plants?",
            "answer": "Flowering and non-flowering."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 47,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are egg-laying animals called?",
            "answer": "Oviparous."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 48,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are animals that give birth called?",
            "answer": "Viviparous."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 49,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is a tree diagram?",
            "answer": "A diagram with branches to show information."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 50,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Why is it called a tree diagram?",
            "answer": "Because it has branches."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 51,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What does a note promise?",
            "answer": "To give that much money."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 52,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is difficult about stone money?",
            "answer": "Hard to carry."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 53,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is easier about paper money?",
            "answer": "easier to carry."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 54,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Why should we not tear notes?",
            "answer": "Because they are valuable/government property."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 55,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "How do you get money?",
            "answer": "Work hard / Earn it."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 56,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Is silver a precious metal?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 57,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Is plastic a precious metal?",
            "answer": "No."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 58,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'exchange'?",
            "answer": "Giving one thing and getting another."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 59,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are 'wages'?",
            "answer": "Money paid for work."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 60,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are 'cowries'?",
            "answer": "Small shells used as money."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 61,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What are 'implements'?",
            "answer": "Tools."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 62,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is an 'autobiography'?",
            "answer": "Life story written by oneself."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 63,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is the symbol for Rupee?",
            "answer": "₹."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 64,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is the symbol for Dollar?",
            "answer": "$."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 65,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is the symbol for Pound?",
            "answer": "£."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 66,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What note is mentioned in the autobiography question?",
            "answer": "Hundred-rupee note."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 67,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What comes after 'She was tired' but...?",
            "answer": "She finished her homework."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 68,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What comes after 'She wanted to buy a car' but...?",
            "answer": "She had no money."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 69,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What comes after 'He was angry' but...?",
            "answer": "He did not fight."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 70,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What comes after 'He did not know the answer' but...?",
            "answer": "He did not copy."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 71,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'crumple'?",
            "answer": "Crush or wrinkle."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 72,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'damage'?",
            "answer": "Harm or spoil."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 73,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'spent'?",
            "answer": "Used money."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 74,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Where is England?",
            "answer": "Europe (implied context of country using pounds)."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 75,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Where is the United States?",
            "answer": "North America (implied)."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 76,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is the page number?",
            "answer": "68-70."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 77,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What unit is this chapter?",
            "answer": "Unit 4."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 78,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Is 'furniture' a living thing?",
            "answer": "No."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 79,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Is a cat a living thing?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 80,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Do birds lay eggs?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 81,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Do mammals lay eggs (generally)?",
            "answer": "No."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 82,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'rubbish'?",
            "answer": "Waste material."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 83,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'salary'?",
            "answer": "Regular payment for work."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 84,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'labour'?",
            "answer": "Work."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 85,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'grain' used for?",
            "answer": "Food and barter."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 86,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Who works for us?",
            "answer": "People we pay."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 87,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What did people carry before paper money?",
            "answer": "Heavy coins/stones."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 88,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Is money important?",
            "answer": "Yes, to buy things."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 89,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "Can you use Indian Rupees in USA?",
            "answer": "No, they use dollars."
        },
        {
            "question_id": 90,
            "question_type": "SHORT",
            "question": "What is 'precious'?",
            "answer": "Of great value."
        }
    ]
}